<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Fish_Project</string>
    <string name="title_activity_viewer">Viewer</string>
    <string name="large_text">
        "Material is the metaphor.\n\n"

        "A material metaphor is the unifying theory of a rationalized space and a system of motion."
        "The material is grounded in tactile reality, inspired by the study of paper and ink, yet "
        "technologically advanced and open to imagination and magic.\n"
        "Surfaces and edges of the material provide visual cues that are grounded in reality. The "
        "use of familiar tactile attributes helps users quickly understand affordances. Yet the "
        "flexibility of the material creates new affordances that supercede those in the physical "
        "world, without breaking the rules of physics.\n"
        "The fundamentals of light, surface, and movement are key to conveying how objects move, "
        "interact, and exist in space and in relation to each other. Realistic lighting shows "
        "seams, divides space, and indicates moving parts.\n\n"

        "Bold, graphic, intentional.\n\n"

        "The foundational elements of print based design typography, grids, space, scale, color, "
        "and use of imagery guide visual treatments. These elements do far more than please the "
        "eye. They create hierarchy, meaning, and focus. Deliberate color choices, edge to edge "
        "imagery, large scale typography, and intentional white space create a bold and graphic "
        "interface that immerse the user in the experience.\n"
        "An emphasis on user actions makes core functionality immediately apparent and provides "
        "waypoints for the user.\n\n"

        "Motion provides meaning.\n\n"

        "Motion respects and reinforces the user as the prime mover. Primary user actions are "
        "inflection points that initiate motion, transforming the whole design.\n"
        "All action takes place in a single environment. Objects are presented to the user without "
        "breaking the continuity of experience even as they transform and reorganize.\n"
        "Motion is meaningful and appropriate, serving to focus attention and maintain continuity. "
        "Feedback is subtle yet clear. Transitions are efﬁcient yet coherent.\n\n"

        "3D world.\n\n"

        "The material environment is a 3D space, which means all objects have x, y, and z "
        "dimensions. The z-axis is perpendicularly aligned to the plane of the display, with the "
        "positive z-axis extending towards the viewer. Every sheet of material occupies a single "
        "position along the z-axis and has a standard 1dp thickness.\n"
        "On the web, the z-axis is used for layering and not for perspective. The 3D world is "
        "emulated by manipulating the y-axis.\n\n"

        "Light and shadow.\n\n"

        "Within the material environment, virtual lights illuminate the scene. Key lights create "
        "directional shadows, while ambient light creates soft shadows from all angles.\n"
        "Shadows in the material environment are cast by these two light sources. In Android "
        "development, shadows occur when light sources are blocked by sheets of material at "
        "various positions along the z-axis. On the web, shadows are depicted by manipulating the "
        "y-axis only. The following example shows the card with a height of 6dp.\n\n"

        "Resting elevation.\n\n"

        "All material objects, regardless of size, have a resting elevation, or default elevation "
        "that does not change. If an object changes elevation, it should return to its resting "
        "elevation as soon as possible.\n\n"

        "Component elevations.\n\n"

        "The resting elevation for a component type is consistent across apps (e.g., FAB elevation "
        "does not vary from 6dp in one app to 16dp in another app).\n"
        "Components may have different resting elevations across platforms, depending on the depth "
        "of the environment (e.g., TV has a greater depth than mobile or desktop).\n\n"

        "Responsive elevation and dynamic elevation offsets.\n\n"

        "Some component types have responsive elevation, meaning they change elevation in response "
        "to user input (e.g., normal, focused, and pressed) or system events. These elevation "
        "changes are consistently implemented using dynamic elevation offsets.\n"
        "Dynamic elevation offsets are the goal elevation that a component moves towards, relative "
        "to the component’s resting state. They ensure that elevation changes are consistent "
        "across actions and component types. For example, all components that lift on press have "
        "the same elevation change relative to their resting elevation.\n"
        "Once the input event is completed or cancelled, the component will return to its resting "
        "elevation.\n\n"

        "Avoiding elevation interference.\n\n"

        "Components with responsive elevations may encounter other components as they move between "
        "their resting elevations and dynamic elevation offsets. Because material cannot pass "
        "through other material, components avoid interfering with one another any number of ways, "
        "whether on a per component basis or using the entire app layout.\n"
        "On a component level, components can move or be removed before they cause interference. "
        "For example, a floating action button (FAB) can disappear or move off screen before a "
        "user picks up a card, or it can move if a snackbar appears.\n"
        "On the layout level, design your app layout to minimize opportunities for interference. "
        "For example, position the FAB to one side of stream of a cards so the FAB won’t interfere "
        "when a user tries to pick up one of cards.\n\n"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_1_name">
        "ASOKA PETHIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_1">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Systomus asoka</i></h3> \n
        <li>    <b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li>    <b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Asoka Barb</li>
        <li>    <b>Sinhala name</b> :- Ran manissa, Asoka pethiya</li>
        <li>    <b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR </li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_1_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li>    <b>Location</b> :- Found in upper reaches of the Sitawaka River and Kithulgala area on Kelani river  </li>
        <li>    <b>Environment</b> :- Found in fast flowing well-oxygenated clear waters with 1 to 2m depths having sandy or gravelly substrates</li>
        <li>    <b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 14 cm</li>
        <li>    <b>Identification features</b> :-
        <br>Horizontally elongated blotch found on caudal peduncle</br>
        <br>Top and bottom margins of caudal fin are red</br>
        <br>Other fins are transparent with yellow color</br>
        <br>Two pairs of barbels present</br>
        <br>5-7 black strips running on lateral side along the body</br>
	    </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :-  Conservation of these species very important due to decline population and restricted to few places</li>
          ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_2_name">
        "DUMBARA PETHIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_2">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Systomus martenstyni</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Martenstyn\'s Barb</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Dumbara pethiya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
         <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
         ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_2_1">
        <![CDATA[
         <li><b>Location</b> :- Found in Knuckles mountain range and tributaries of River Mahaweli: Loggal Oya and Badulu Oya</li>
         <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in Shaded or unshaded mid-hill streams with sandy or rocky substrates</li>
         <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 12cm</li>
         <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
         <br>Black horizontal blotch present on caudal peduncle</br>
         <br>Lateral line complete</br>
         <br>Two pairs of barbels but no tubercles on the snout</br>
         <br>Fins are transparent with red/orange color</br>
	</li>
         <li><b>Other</b> :-  This species can be overlapping with Systomus asoka</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_3_name">
        "DANKUDA PETHIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_3">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Dawkinsia srilankensis</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Blotched Filamented Barb</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Dankuda pethiya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_3_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b> :- Restricted to the Knuckles mountain range and tributaries of River Mahaweli, Kuda Oya and Amban Ganga</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in fast flowing streams with sandy substrates</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 10cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Three distinct black blotches in adults</br>
        <br>Terminal mouth/br>
        <br>Black spot is present on the base of dorsal fin</br>
        <br>Matured males have a filamentous dorsal fin with 3-5 black</br>
        <br>Elongated rays</br></li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :-  Juveniles have 4-5 black cross bars across body. When matured fade in to 3 exiting blotches</li>

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_4_name">
        "BANDULA PETHIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_4">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Pethia bandula</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Bandula Barb</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Jayanthiya, Bandula pethiya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_4_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Restricted to Minimaru Colaniya in Pallegama Estate near Galapitamada</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in slow flowing, shallow streams that flowing through rice field and rubber plantation with sandy and muddy substrates</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 4.5cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Have two vertical black blotches on the body</br>
        <br>Lateral line is incomplete</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- Females are in lighter color</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_5_name">
        "GADAYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_5">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Labeo fisheri</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Mountain Labeo</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Gadaya, Loku gadaya, Kalu gadaya, Weli gadaya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018): EN</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_5_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in upper reaches of Mahaweli river</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Prefer deep rocky pools habitats in fast flowing mountain rivers</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 24 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Two pairs of barbels are present</br>
        <br>Dark black blotch found on caudal peduncle</br>
        <br>Have inferior sucker like mouth with thick fleshy lips</br>
        <br>Origin of dorsal fin close to tip of snout than caudal</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b>  :-  N/A</li>

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_6_name">
        "THAMBALAYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_6">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Labeo lankae</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Orange-Fin Labeo</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Thambalaya, Thambalaya vanna</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_6_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in Mahaweli and Amban rivers</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Prefer deep rocky pools habitats in fast flowing mountain rivers</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 20-30 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Only one pair of barbels is present</br>
        <br>Dark black forward pointing blotch found on caudal penuncle</br>
        <br>Have inferior sucker like mouth with thick fleshy lips</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- This species can be overlapping with Systomus martenstyni and Systomus sp.Richmondi</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_7_name">
        "WILPITA DANDIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_7">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Rasbora wilpita</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Wilpita Rasbora</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Wilpita dandiya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): EN</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_7_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in Kelani to Nilwala river basins</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in Shaded slow flowing streams with muddy or leafy substrates</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 8 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Elongated body with terminal mouth</br>
        <br>Prominent symphysial knob on lower jaw</br>
        <br>Conspicuous lateral processes on premaxillary</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- No sexual dimorphism</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_8_name">
        "PULLI AHIRAVA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_8">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Lepidocephalichthys jonklaasi</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cobitidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Jonklaas\'s Loach</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Ahirava, Pulli ahirava</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018):</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_8_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in Kelani to Nilwala river basins/li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in Shaded slow flowing streams with muddy or leafy substrates</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 5 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features  :-</b>
        <br>There is a dark stripe from eye to upper lip/br>
        <br>Three pairs of barbels present</br>
        <br>Vertically elongated blotch on the end of caudal peduncle</br>

        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- This species can be overlapping with Lepidocephalichthys thermalis</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_9_name">
        "MALPULUTTA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_9">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Malpulutta kretseris</i></h3>
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Belontidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Ornate Paradise Fish</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Malpulutta</li>
         <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018) : LC-</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_9_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in Kalu to Niwala river basins</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in small, shallow, slow flowing silted streams</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 4 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :- </b>
        <br>Dorsal and anal fins are pointed with filaments</br>
        <br>First ray of pelvic fin are elongated with filaments</br>
        <br>2-3 middle rays of lanceololate caudal fin elongated with filaments</br>
        <br>Have two dark lines which start from snout to posterior end of the operculum</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- Females and juveniles lack the elongated filaments and the blue tint on the fins,
        Males are larger and more colorful than females,
        Females and juveniles can be overlapping with Pseudosphromenus
        cupanus</li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_10_name">
        "THOL RATHU WELIGOWWA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_10">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Sicyopus jonklaasi</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Gobiidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Lipstick Gobyb</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Thol rathu weligowwa</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): EN </li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_10_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Global (2018): DD-</b></li>
        <li><b>Location</b>  :- Found in Kelani to Nilwala river basins</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in rocky mid-hill streams with fast flowing water</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 5 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>Male brownish to yellowish with bright red lips</br>
        <br>Bright red colored elliptical blotch found in base of the caudal fin</br>
        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- Females Lack of red color in the body</li>
        <li><b></b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_11_name">
        "GAL WELIGOWWA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_11">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Sicyopterus halei</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Gobiidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Red-Tailed Goby</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Gal weligowwa</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): CR</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018) :DD</b></li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_11_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b> :- Found in Kelani to Gin river basin</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in rocky mid-hill streams with fast flowing water</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 8 cm </li>
        <li><b>Identification features :-</b>
        <br>7-8 dark blotches can be found in dorsal and lateral sides of the body</br>
        <br>Second ray of the first dorsal fin is elongated</br>

        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- N/A</li>
        <li><b></b></li>



        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_12_name">
        "KATA RATHU WELIGOWWA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_12">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Schismatogobius deraniyagalai</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Gobiidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Red-Neck Goby</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Kata rathu weligowwa</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): EN</li>
        <li><b>Global (2018) : DD</b></li>
        ]]>
     </string>
    <string name="pro_12_1">
        <![CDATA[<li><b>Location</b> :- Restricted to wet zone</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in shallow areas of rivers with sandy, coarse sand or gravel substrate</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 4-5 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features :- </b>
        <br>4-5 irregular black spots found along lateral line of the body</br>
        <br>A large, vertically elongated, oval spot at base of caudal fin</br>
        <br>Gape reaching backwards almost to preopercle angle in males and to middle of eye in females</br>
        <br>In males, the chin and throat are orange-red. Inside of mouth of male’s bright red</br>

        </li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- Females are dull in color</li>

        ]]>
    </string>

    <string name="pro_13_name">
        "DANKUDA PETHIYA"
    </string>
    <string name="pro_13">
        <![CDATA[<h3>Scientific name :- <i>Dawkinsia srilankensis</i></h3> \n
        <li><b>Family</b> :- Cyprinidae</li>
        <li><b>English name</b> :- Sri Lanka Blotched Filamented Barb</li>
        <li><b>Sinhala name</b> :- Dankuda pethiya</li>
        <li><b>IUCN Status</b> :- Local (2012): VU </li>
        <li>Global (2018) :</li>
        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="pro_13_1">
        <![CDATA[
        <li><b>Location</b> :- Found in Kalu to Nilwala river basins</li>
        <li><b>Environment</b> :- Found in shaded shallow rivers</li>
        <li><b>Maximum length</b> :- Can be grow up to 10 cm</li>
        <li><b>Identification features</b> :- Pelvic fins are absent</li>
        <li><b>Other</b> :- This species can be overlapping with Channa kelrtii</li>

        ]]>
    </string>
    <string name="title_activity_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- Strings related to Settings -->

    <!-- Example General settings -->
    <string name="pref_header_general">General</string>

    <string name="pref_title_social_recommendations">Enable social recommendations</string>
    <string name="pref_description_social_recommendations">Recommendations for people to contact
        based on your message history
    </string>

    <string name="pref_title_display_name">Display name</string>
    <string name="pref_default_display_name">John Smith</string>

    <string name="pref_title_add_friends_to_messages">Add friends to messages</string>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_titles">
        <item>Always</item>
        <item>When possible</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_example_list_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>0</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <!-- Example settings for Data & Sync -->
    <string name="pref_header_data_sync">Data &amp; sync</string>

    <string name="pref_title_sync_frequency">Sync frequency</string>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_titles">
        <item>15 minutes</item>
        <item>30 minutes</item>
        <item>1 hour</item>
        <item>3 hours</item>
        <item>6 hours</item>
        <item>Never</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pref_sync_frequency_values">
        <item>15</item>
        <item>30</item>
        <item>60</item>
        <item>180</item>
        <item>360</item>
        <item>-1</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entries">
        <item>Entry 1</item>
        <item>Entry 2</item>
        <item>Entry 3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="list_preference_entry_values">
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="multi_select_list_preference_default_value" />

    <string name="pref_title_system_sync_settings">System sync settings</string>

    <!-- Example settings for Notifications -->
    <string name="pref_header_notifications">Notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_new_message_notifications">New message notifications</string>

    <string name="pref_title_ringtone">Ringtone</string>
    <string name="pref_ringtone_silent">Silent</string>

    <string name="pref_title_vibrate">Vibrate</string>

</resources>
